schedulestar.com 2017-10-18

# BigTeams - Privacy Policy - 0

__

  * 

BIGTEAMS PRIVACY POLICY (Rev 6/2017)

BIGTEAMS, LLC (“BIGTEAMS”) provides athletic/activity/scheduling website management service to schools, leagues, booster clubs, and athletic clubs, including through the websites located at www.bigteams.com and www.schedulestar.com. This Privacy Policy is to explain what information about you we collect, how we use it and how we share it. We provide a link to this Policy wherever it applies, such as on our websites, our mobile apps, our social networking presence on Facebook, and other online services that we provide and control (“Services”). By using our Services, you accept our practices as described in this Policy. This Policy is incorporated by reference into the BigTeams Terms of Use (“[TOU](http://bigteams.com/tou)”), which also governs your use of our Services. 

Types of Information We Collect

Information submitted to BIGTEAMS includes personal and non-identifying information collected when interacting with our products. Information can be collected through the use of our services:

  * We collect information automatically about your use of our Services, as well as the devices and software you use to access our Services

  * we use cookies, web beacons and other similar technology to collect information automatically, in order to deliver the Services, tailor your experience, monitor how our Services are used, improve them, deliver customized advertising, and for other purposes. 

  * tracking information such as your browser type, the type of operating system you use, and pages you visited on our sites. 

None of this information identifies you personally; we use this information to make our sites more useable to you, your league and your schools.

Information collected includes:

  * Personal Information

    * Name, email address, phone number, graduation year

  * Non-personal information via cookies, see “Cookies”

We may require certain types of personal information in order to provide a particular Service

We also may collect information about how you use the Services, like when you visit our web sites and how you interact with our content.

You may visit our site anonymously. Personal information is only collected when registering as a user of the website including creation of a fan account, administrative user, and online registration.

How We Use Information

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

  * To send periodic emails

Cookies

We use “cookies” in a very limited way in order to store user information. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. A cookie contains a unique number that allows our site to recognize your computer. The help function on most browsers contains information on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies or to disable cookies entirely. However, if you don’t accept cookies, you may not be able to use some of the functions of the website. 

Provide Services 

Your information will be accessible to BigTeams staff and school administrators who may choose to allow booster club members access to some personally identifiable information in order to, for example, fill orders from the online store. Merchant account providers that handle credit card transactions will also have some access to personally identifiable information. This is necessary to fill orders from the online store. Please contact us for more information about your school’s merchant account provider. These merchant account providers have their own privacy policies. 

Disclosures 

BigTeams may disclose information about you and your use of the Web Site and the BigTeams Services if BigTeams believes such disclosure is reasonably necessary

  * To comply with the law or legal process

  * To protect or defend the rights or property of BigTeams or others

  * To enforce the BigTeams TOU or this Policy

  * To respond to claims that the content(s) of a communication violates the rights of another. 

Reports 

We periodically prepare analyses and reports reflecting visitor and member use of the Web Site and BigTeams Services for our internal use as well as for a limited number of our business partners. These reports include aggregate (non-personal) information about BigTeams members, and in certain instances, visitors to the Web Site. The information in these reports will not identify you individually. Our business partners who have access to these reports will not be able to contact you from the information contained in the reports. 

Third Party Advertisers 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. Most advertisements you see on the Web Site are served to your web browser by BigTeams. However, BigTeams allows other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Web Site or through BigTeams Services. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. We only authorize our third-party ad networks to employ anonymous cookies for ad delivery and anonymous targeting. Our third-party ad servers do not collect, nor do we give them access to, any personally identifying information about you. BigTeams also limits the type of ads delivered by these ad networks so that they are appropriate for children. Third Party advertising networks may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. BigTeams may also include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by BigTeams to assist with auditing, research and reporting for advertisers.  Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. If you want to prevent a third-party ad server from sending and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each ad network’s web site individually and opt out (if they offer this capability). Please contact us if you would like additional information regarding the specific third-party ad networks used on the Web Site. 

Third Party Affiliates

This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. 

In addition BigTeams may share or transfer information about you and that you provide to BigTeams, to one or more third party entities pursuant to a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion, or all of, the assets or stock of BigTeams or its affiliated entities, or as otherwise provided herein. 

CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. 

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

  * We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.

  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:  

  * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses

  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way

  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters

  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly

  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email  

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, there are unsubscribe options with all email and text communications as well as controls within accounts. If you have any issues please contact us at support@bigteams.com.

California Residents

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. This document represents our compliance with CalOPPA.

Security 

BigTeams takes every reasonable precaution to protect our users’ information. When you submit information via our service, your information is protected both online and offline. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. However, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and BigTeams will not be intercepted by others and that information stored on our servers will be free from unauthorized access. While we have taken reasonable precautions to protect this information, you should always use discretion in what information you send to us and not expect that such information will be absolutely free from intrusion. If you have any questions about the security of our service, please contact us. 

Children 

BigTeams is committed to the safety of children. Children under the age of 13 may not register or participate in any of the BigTeams Services. If children under 18 elect to register in any of the BigTeams Services, they should ask a parent for permission before sending any information to the Web Site. We will not request or knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from a child under 13. We offer our Services to individuals who are at least 18 years old. We do not knowingly collect personal information online from children under 13 years of age. If we discover that we have inadvertently collected personal information online from children under the age of 13, we will endeavor promptly to destroy or remove any identifying details. 

Links

You should be aware that when you are on the Web Site or when you receive emails sent as part of BigTeams Services, you could be directed to other sites beyond our control, and beyond the school/booster club’s control. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and affiliates that may use the Web Site’s logo. These other web sites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. 

Notification of Changes and Your Acceptance of the Policy

By using a BigTeams website, application or services, you signify your agreement to the terms of this Policy and the [TOU](http://bigteams.com/tou). We may change this Policy from time to time. We will post any changes to this page, and if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. We will not reduce the protection given to your personal information under this Policy without giving you an opportunity to consent to our continued use of your personal information. 

Contact us if you have any questions about this policy at: 

BigTeams, LLC

PO Box 2878, Reston, VA  20195.

The BigTeams app lets student-athletes, parents, and fans stay up to date on their school and favorite teams while on the go. Get the latest schedules, rosters, scores, and upload photos directly from the app!

Available FREE for [](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/bigteams/id445479124?mt=8) [](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.bigteams.droid)
